{"data":[{"question":"We will go for a walk in the Grand Park tomorrow, weather ___.","a":"permitting","b":"to permit","c":"permitted","d":"having permitted","answer":"1","explain":"\n- A present participle attributes a quality of action to the noun, which is viewed as undertaking the action \n- When a participle phrase concludes a main clause and modifies a word farther up in the sentence, you will need a comma","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"___ that the train is gone, it is useless to wait.","a":"Seen","b":"Seeing","c":"Having seen","d":"To see","answer":"2","explain":"\n- A present participle attributes a quality of action to the noun, which is viewed as undertaking the action \n- When a participle phrase concludes a main clause and modifies a word farther up in the sentence, you will need a comma","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"My letter,___ to the wrong number, reached him late.","a":"to have addressed","b":"being addressed","c":"having been addressed","d":"to have been addressed","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- A past participle views the noun as having undergone the action expressed by the participle\n\n- When a participle phrase concludes a main clause and is describing the word right in front of it, you need no punctuation to connect the two sentence parts\n\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"He wanted a basket of flowers ___ to his wife","a":"sending","b":"sent","c":"to send","d":"to have sent","answer":"2","explain":"\n- A past participle views the noun as having undergone the action expressed by the participle \n- When a participle phrase concludes a main clause and is describing the word right in front of it, you need no punctuation to connect the two sentence parts ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"When I returned home, I found the window open and something ___.","a":"to steal","b":"stealing","c":"stolen","d":"stole","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb (with to) :you find \/see or watch the whole action \n- Find\/ see\/ watch...+ Verb_ing : you find \/see or watch part of the action","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"My father encouraged me in my painting, but never lived to see any of my works ___ in public.","a":"exhibiting","b":"exhibited","c":"having exhibited","d":"exhibit","answer":"2","explain":"\n- A past participle views the noun as having undergone the action expressed by the participle","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Standing,___ on a hill, his villa commands a fine view.","a":"as it is","b":"as it was","c":"as he does","d":"as it does","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- As it does= as it stands","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Hidden ___ by a big tree , his house was not to be seen.","a":"as it was","b":"as it is","c":"as it did","d":"as he did","answer":"1","explain":"\n- As it was= As it was hidden","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Walking along the riverside path, ___.","a":"I met several groups of hikers","b":"the river met several groups of hikers","c":"it was several groups of hikers","d":"we met by several groups of hikers","answer":"1","explain":"\n- \" I\" is the person who was walking along the riverside path","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Asked if he could come to the party that night, ___.","a":"nobody said anything.","b":"they did not get an answer from him.","c":"nothing was said by him.","d":"Tom nodded his head and left the room.","answer":"4","explain":"\n- \" Tom\" is the person who \"was asked if he could come to the party\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"55","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}